##### ONLINE PAYMENT CENTER

×

To make a loan payment, [**click here**](https://lafcu.messagepay.com/payment/accountlookup) then enter the requested information to make a one-time or recurring payment 24/7 from an account at another financial institution.

Close

 **Due to scheduled maintenance, Mobile and Online banking, After Hours Phone Center and ATMs (limited) will NOT be available Sunday, November 17 from 3am to 7am PST.** 

Close Alert

We use cookies on our site to provide the optimum user experience. By using this website, you agree to the use of cookies on this site. [Read our privacy policy.](https://www.lafcu.org/privacypolicies)

Close Alert

Accounts

Loans & Credit

Services

About Us

Search LOGIN

Online Banking
--------------

Username  

Menu toggle

Close mobile menu [Home](https://www.lafcu.org/)Accounts

Loans & Credit

Services

About Us

As of 11-14-24

Privacy Policy
==============

| FACTS | WHAT DOES LOS ANGELES FEDERAL CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION? |
| --- | --- |
| Why? | Financial companies choose how they share Your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires Us to tell You how We collect, share, and protect Your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what We do. |
| What? | The types of personal information We collect and share depend on the product or service You have with Us. This information can include:  <br>• Social Security number and income  <br>• account balances and payment history  <br>• credit history and credit scores |
| How? | All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information, the reasons Los Angeles Federal Credit Union chooses to share, and whether You can limit this sharing. |

| Reasons We can share Your personal information | Does the Credit Union share? | Can You limit this sharing? |
| --- | --- | --- |
| For Our everyday business purposes – such as to process Your transactions, maintain Your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureau | YES | NO  |
| For Our marketing purposes - to offer Our products and services to You | YES | YES |
| For joint marketing with other financial companies | YES | YES |
| For Our affiliates’ everyday business purposes - Information about Your transactions and experiences | NO  | WE DON'T SHARE |
| For Our affiliates’ everyday business purposes - Information about Your creditworthiness | NO  | WE DON'T SHARE |
| For Our affiliates to market to You | NO  | WE DON'T SHARE |
| For non-affiliates to market to You | NO  | WE DON'T SHARE |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| To limit Our sharing | Please note:  <br>If You are a _new member_, We can begin sharing Your information 30 days from the date We sent this notice. When You are no longer Our member, we will discontinue sharing your information as described in this notice.  <br>However, You can contact Us at any time to limit Our sharing.  <br>• Call (877) 695-2328, or  <br>• Email Us at: memberservices@lafcu.org |
| Questions: | Call (877) 695-2328 |

| What We do | no text |
| --- | --- |
| How does Los Angeles Federal Credit Union protect my personal information? | To protect Your personal information from unauthorized access and use. We use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. |
| How does Los Angeles Federal Credit Union collect my personal information? | We collect Your personal information, for example, when You  <br>• open an account or deposit money  <br>• pay Your bills or apply for a loan  <br>• use Your credit or debit card  <br>We also collect Your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or others |
| Why can’t I limit all sharing? | Federal law gives You the right to limit only  <br>• sharing for affiliates everyday business purposes – information about Your creditworthiness  <br>• affiliates from using Your information to market to You  <br>• sharing for non-affiliates to market to You  <br>State laws and individual companies may give You additional rights to limit sharing. |
| What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else? | Your choices will apply to everyone on Your account. |

| Definitions | no text |
| --- | --- |
| Affiliates | Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies. Our affiliates include financial companies such as C.O.L.A. Insurance Services Corporation. |
| Non-Affiliates | Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies. Los Angeles Federal Credit Union does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you. |
| Joint-Marketing | A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to You. Our joint marketing partners include categories of companies, such as:  <br>• financial service providers  <br>• insurance companies |

| Other Important Information |     |
| --- | --- |
| **For California Residents:** | We will provide a separate short form notice describing the rights of California residents to opt-out of the sharing of your non-public personal information in accordance with the California Financial Information Privacy Act (Cal FIPA). We have also provided a separate Consumer Privacy Notice notifying you of your rights under the California Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and the [California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (CCPA) on our website](https://www.lafcu.org/privacypolicies/california-consumer-privacy-act-ccpa).<br><br>. |
| **For Vermont Residents:** | Under Vermont law, we will not share information we collect about Vermont residents with companies outside of our corporate family, unless the law allows. For example, we may share information with your consent, to service your accounts or under joint marketing agreements with other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements. We will not share information about your creditworthiness within our corporate family except with your consent, but we may share information about our transactions or experiences with you within our corporate family without your consent.<br><br>1\. Please note that the requirements for Vermont in 8 V.S.A. § 10204 et. seq. mandate that the Credit Union and its CUSOs not share financial information with nonaffiliated entities without an opt-in from the consumer. An opt-in is also required for sharing financial information among affiliates if such financial information is considered a “credit report” under 9 V.S.A. § 10204a or a “consumer report” under the FCRA, both of which have similar definitions that includes any written, oral, or other communication of any information bearing on a consumer’s<br><br>creditworthiness, credit standing, credit capacity, character, general reputation, personal characteristics, or mode of living. If you require additional information on these Vermont requirements and need help drafting state-specific opt-ins for Vermont residents, please advise us in writing. |

Socialize With Us
-----------------

Important Links
---------------

Protected By
------------

_If you are using a screen reader or other auxiliary aid and are having problems using this website, call (877) 695-2328 for assistance 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. During business hours you can also visit any of our physical branches where we can assist you further, since all products, services and information on this website are also available at any branch._

_© 2024 Los Angeles Federal Credit Union_
